congratulations on making it to the end
恭喜你坚持到了最后
of this short course
在这个短期课程中
in summary in this short course you've Learned about
在这个简短的课程中总结一下
two key principles for prompting
提示的两个关键原则
right clearance
正确的间隙
specific instructions and when it's appropriate
具体的指示和适当的时间
give them all the time to think
给他们足够的时间思考
you also Learned about iterative
你也学到了迭代
prompt development
迅速发展
and how having a process to get to the prompt is right
以及如何使用一个过程来获得提示是正确的
for your application is key
对于您的应用程序是关键
and we went through
我们经历了
a few capabilities of large
几个大的能力
language models that are useful for many applications
对许多应用程序都有用的语言模型
specifically summarizing inferring
特别是总结推断
transforming and expanding
转型拓展
and you also saw how to build a custom chatbot
您还看到了如何构建自定义聊天机器人
that was a lot
这是很多
that you Learned in just one short course
你在一门短期课程中学到的东西
and I hope you enjoyed going through these materials
我希望你们喜欢这些材料
we hope you'll come up with some
我们希望你能想出一些
ideas for applications that you can
应用程序的想法，你可以
build yourself now
现在就塑造自己
and please go try this out and let us
请试一下，让我们
know what you come up with
知道你想出了什么
no application is too small
没有一个应用程序是太小的
it's you know
你知道的
fine to start with something that's kind of
很好，从一些有点
a very
一个非常
small project with maybe a little bit of utility
一个小项目，可能有点实用
or maybe it's not even useful at all
或者它根本没用
it's just something fun
这只是一些有趣的事情
yeah and I find
是的，我发现
playing with these models actually really fun
玩这些模型真的很有趣
so go play with it
所以去玩吧
yeah I agree it's a good weekend activity
是的，我同意这是一个很好的周末活动
speaking from experience
从经验来看
and just you know
你知道
please
请
use the learnings from your first project to build
使用从第一个项目中学到的知识来构建
about the second project and
关于第二个项目和
you know maybe even about the third project
你甚至可能知道第三个项目
so on that's kind of how I have kind of
这就是我如何
grown over time using these models myself as well
随着时间的推移，我自己也在使用这些模型
or if you have an idea for a bigger project already
或者你已经有了一个更大的项目的想法
just go for it
大胆去做吧
and you know as a reminder
作为一个提醒
these kind of large
这些很大
language models are a very powerful technology
语言模型是一项非常强大的技术
so it kind of goes without saying that we
所以不用说，我们
ask you to use them responsibly
要求你负责任地使用它们
and please
请
only build things that will have a positive impact
只建造会产生积极影响的东西
fully agree I think in this age
我完全同意，我认为在这个时代
people that built AI
建造人工智能的人
systems can have a huge impact on others
系统可以对其他人产生巨大的影响
so it's more important than ever that all of us
所以比以往任何时候都更重要的是我们所有人
only use these tools responsibly
负责任地使用这些工具
and I think
我认为
building launch language model
构建启动语言模型
based applications is just a very
基于应用程序只是一个非常
exciting and drawing view right now
令人兴奋的和绘图视图现在
and now that you've finished this course
现在你已经完成了这门课
I think you now have a wealth of knowledge
我认为你现在拥有丰富的知识
to let you build
让你建造
things that few people today know how to
现在很少有人知道怎么做
so I hope you also help us to
所以我希望你也能帮助我们
spread the word and encourage others
传播信息，鼓励他人
to take this course too
也要上这门课
in closing I hope you had fun during this course
最后，我希望你们在这门课上玩得开心
and I want to thank you
我想谢谢你
for finishing this course
完成本课程
and both easy
都很简单
and I look forward to hearing about the amazing things
我很期待听到这些神奇的事情
that you build
你所建造的